That's what
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Do
that salt and friends today we will talk
about banks illegal quality and
further in this video I will tell you
what are the advantages and disadvantages of taking a policy from the bank and
you can contact
me for any information whatever
difference remains and if you are
watching my videos then please subscribe to my channel
please
like the video and press the bell icon
latest updates video Stree ka Ras
you don't get Babu your every organization Kajal
and now let's talk about these politics
you all know
how big a role banks play in our lives we
open our accounts in banks we also
provide you 65 we also
send money if needed people also take money we also take
balance so basically all this work is related to
balance and in this field
banks basically install apps
this is a way of business to
earn profit there is nothing wrong in it everyone's
eyes are on doing business so if
any product is launched from that side then friends  It
simply means that banks make profits.
Now we want to know what are the
benefits of the policies given through banks.
First of all, the premium of these policies is
very low. True policies are
available, hence they attract more people in distress.
Secondly, there is very little paper work.
When we take a policy through banks,
companies enter into a deal with banks
because banks have a good customer
base and companies give huge profits to the bank.
Companies have a good customer base.
Companies design fancy policies
whose premium is slightly lower than the market.
Therefore, in the bank, you are always offered
offers of low premiums, due to which you get
tempted to buy a policy after 10 years. If you
want to buy this policy, then
this is a policy with group benefits.
Friends, if the
company's reputation ends with the bond, then
your policy will also not continue at
any cost. IRDA has some
questions for this, but still
some clear Google time has not come for this.
Now in such a situation, the tenure of the job company
ends.  If you have a bank then in such a situation your policy can
end at any time, in some cases
companies can think like this if you also have a medical
condition, but if you also have medical
instability, your medical condition is
not good then you can have a problem, your
policy can also get stuck, now
related to this, I remembered a small thing here, I
think I should share with you,
friends, what happened recently, there is a
question from Maharashtra, I
live in a small town there, I got a call from them, so
friends, I was asking to open an account in the bank,
along with the account, a full
health insurance policy was also given, the
premium of the policy was very low and the paper
work was
equal to Yamuna, Path Suri policy was taken,
Shakti Polythene, we did not have some paper time, so he continued
his policy for 4 years, he paid the
premium, after 4 years, now some
time ago Kunkalim came, his son had fever, regarding that,
his son had to be
admitted to the hospital, the doctor
prepared his report, as soon as the tehsil, his
son was treated, the plan
went for the process, you  It has been two months since the incident and
even after two months the police have
not found out what had
happened to their love and they had called us
and when I called the customer SIM through
conference call, it was also not easy,
that person did not even know how to talk to the customer care, he was
not able to understand how to do it, customer care
said it very well, they
started their verification and even in this process
they took 15 minutes,
when it came to the proposal form, it was
not matching, his number was wrong, his
address was wrong, they changed it and made a
joke of themselves, then somehow his
proposal form verification was
completed, he told his claim IT, only then the
customer care would reduce
that his claim has been rejected by the company
and in the vision they told that
whatever the proposal form is, this question is
complete, the company was not told that the
children got any cricketing, that is why
their music was rejected, so friends I
want to ask you people
whose fault is it  This is about those customers who did not follow anything, the
bank people who
told what to become in the proposal form, how did they
tell, then the roots of the company were
rejected, see friends, the company will definitely
provide the cream, this is the job of the company, but the
company will verify your medical condition
score on a regular basis, this is their right, the
company will verify every small thing of yours on these days
and if
you have made any mistake anywhere in the proposal form, then definitely your
center will be on reaction, now friends,
such a policy in this which also goes through the bank,
what to do on this route, it totally
depends on you how you will
set the film with the company because no third
person will come between you, neither the bank will provide
you any assistance or guidance in this regard, the
branch manager has
no role in your statement agreement,
friends, this is a service issue, service matters,
you are not given any service recording through the bank,
taking pinch volume, friends, it is not an easy thing,
friend, service matters a lot
and perhaps that is why the word of mouth and this
thing makes their premium so cheap  It is
very less because there
you have to do everything yourself, you will
not be given any subsidy. Secondly, it has
also been seen
that when policies are given by the bank, then many
times it is done without going to the medical.
Suppose you have a
pre-existing condition before taking the policy, such as blood
pressure and diabetes.
You have not mentioned this in the proposal form. If you
take a clean policy from the company, then in such a case your claim may be
rejected because at the time of claim the company will definitely verify your medical history. Due to incomplete disclosure in the proposal form, your claim may be rejected. Friends, you
yourself should talk to 45 banks near you,
you will yourself know that you were
running a Feng Shui policy 10 years ago, the
bank has terminated it and you have got a new
company sale. What
happens to the policy, the term of its completion is
very less. The policies that go through the bank run very comfortably for 27 years, four to five years,
after that when the policy alarm starts
Yes, the company faces problems
because the premium that the company receives is
very less, the plane is more, hence the
profits and inflow of the company gets spoiled, this is the
reason that the company
ends its coordination with the bank, ending the term
means that your policy can also be lost,
now at the time of delivery, you should
directly take the policy from the company, in that
you have a lot of terms and conditions,
if you are a medical person then you can get it,
if you also have a medical condition, then you
can face problems, so it's total up
to you, have you taken the benefit
of group benefits with cheap and low premium or have to
take a standalone policy, there is a lot of difference between turn on voice
mail and a group benefits policy,
our elders always
say it right, friends, power of Rohit is
expensive and oil is once,
friends, that's all for now in this video,
friends, I would like to say my last salute, this
follow his job is taken through the bank, neither the
interests are minuted nor is there any
fixed time, this is a group benefit,
if the term of the policy is over then your
policy  If you can sleep, then
definitely keep this in mind that if you are planning a policy for yourself
and your family and
you want to get more information about it, then
you can comment in the comment box
or
you can also ask me your question with the help of the WhatsApp number appearing on the screen.
If you found the information that I have given you in this video useful, then
please subscribe to my channel.
Please like the video and
press the bell icon so that
you will keep getting the latest updates. With regards to Will Give,
thank you very much for staying with us in this video.